rozee.pk 2013-05-25

# Privacy Policy - Jobs in Pakistan, Careers in Pakistan, Jobs, Employment, Careers | ROZEE.PK

| 

_Effective Date: 10/20/2008 ROZEE.PK is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.rozee.pk. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at support@ROZEE.PKsatisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

_  
---  
   
**Policy Overview**  
ROZEE.PK takes the privacy of its users very seriously. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Policy details the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to the ROZEE.PK web site and does not apply to information we collect in any other form.

The ROZEE.PK site contains links to other web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites to which you choose to link from our site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.  

**Usage and Information Collection by ROZEE.PK**  
When you create profile by registering on our site, we request the following personally identifiable information from you: your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, physical address, and date of birth. We also collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as gender, interests and favorites.

We also gather information about our users' use of ROZEE.PK, such as what areas of the site you visit and what services you access. We collect your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, as well as administer the site in order to constantly improve the quality of our site and service to you. We may also track and analyze aggregate usage and volume statistics from our site to improve the services we offer on our site. None of this information is linked to your personally identifiable information.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about ROZEE.PK or refer a job posting to a friend, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the ROZEE.PK website or view the job posting. This information is used for no other purpose than to send out this one time email. We provide you two options to allow you to refer your friends to our site. When you choose to access your email account from your ROZEE.PK account, and send your personal contacts an email, we only use the email information you select by checking the box next to each email to service your request to send this one time email from your account. 

We do not store any email information from your email account without your explicit consent. You can also enter a friend's email directly into the 'Invite Colleagues' email field. We do not store this information nor is it shared with any third parties for their promotional purposes.  

**Our Use of Your Information**  
We use the information we gather on ROZEE.PK, whether personal, demographic, aggregate or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the ROZEE.PK web site, creating a positive user experience, and delivering the tools and services that we offer.

We use your email information to send you notifications from our site that you elect to receive such as job alerts along with email newsletters. We send notification emails rarely such as to notify you of any technical issues or service related issues that may affect your access to the site. You generally cannot opt-out of these kinds of communications. You can opt out of receiving newsletters from our site by clicking unsubscribe link at the bottom. If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.We obtain your explicit consent prior to posting your testimonial on our site.  

**Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties**  
We do not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for their promotional purposes.  
  
  * We use third party service providers to administer some of our services to you on our site. We use third party service providers to administer payments and process your credit card information when you purchase our products & services. We also use a third party service provider to host our website as well as serve you with our newsletters via email. These service providers are not authorized to use your personally identifiable information for their promotional purposes.
  * We disclose information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process such as in complying with a judicial proceeding, court order or subpoena; (b) protect our copyrights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.
  * In the event of a sale or merger of our business, your information would be a part of the assets transferred. In addition, in the event we become the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. In the event of any such circumstances, you will be notified via email or through a prominent notice posted on the ROZEE.PK Website.
  * We use a service provider to host our "Help" and "Contact Us" functions on the web site. While these functions take you to a third party web site the information collected here is governed by ROZEE.PK and our privacy practices.

**Personal Information on Resumes and Profiles**  
Since ROZEE.PK is a career site, we give you two options regarding the accessibility of your resume:  
  
  * You can store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by potential employers. This means that you can use it to apply for a job online; however employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database.
  * If you have a confidential resume, but apply to a job posting on ROZEE.PK, the employer to whom you send your resume will be able to view your contact information.

We attempt to limit access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) only to registered employers, recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals.

You may remove your resume on ROZEE.PK or delete your profile on ROZEE.PK at anytime, but, employers, recruiters and others who have access to 

resume database as well as parties who have otherwise gained access may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes or profiles in these instances.  
   
**Posting to Public Areas of ROZEE.PK**  
Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of ROZEE.PK such as the searchable resume database, such information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of ROZEE.PK.  
   
**Use of Cookies**  
We use "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize ROZEE.PK pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When you return to ROZEE.PK, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on ROZEE.PK .  

**Modification of Your Information**  
You may review, correct, update or change your ROZEE.PK account profile at any time on your 'My Settings' page or by emailing our webmaster at 'support@rozee.pk' or by calling customer support at +92-42-5777630. These points of contact also allow you to edit your subscription to our newsletters and promotional emails.

If you opted to receive job postings, commercial e-mails or other communications from ROZEE.PK or third parties at the time you created a ROZEE.PK account, but subsequently change your mind, you may opt-out by editing your ROZEE.PK Account Profile as described above. If you previously opted not to receive such communications, you may later opt-in by editing your ROZEE.PK Account Profile as well.

We retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use of ROZEE.PK, practical, and relevant. Of course, you can delete your resume from ROZEE.PK's online database and close your ROZEE.PK account at any time by informing us via our feedback form. In such an event we will remove all our copies of your resume from ROZEE.PK, your ROZEE.PK account information and remove your profile, except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the Internet.  

**Security of the Profile Information**  
We have implemented commercially reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.  
   
**Use of Material**  
The contents of ROZEE.PK (the "Website") such as text, graphics, images, logos, button icons, software and other material are protected under Pakistan and foreign copyright, trademark and other laws. All material is the property of Naseeb Online Services or its content suppliers or clients. The collection, arrangement and assembly of all content on this Website is the exclusive property of Naseeb Online Services and is protected by Pakistan and international copyright laws. You may not sell or modify the content on the Website or reproduce, display, publicly perform, distribute, or otherwise use its material in any way for any public or commercial purpose. The use of the content on any other Web Site or in a networked computer environment for any purpose is prohibited.  
   
**Children's use of ROZEE.PK**  
The ROZEE.PK web site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.  
   
**Privacy Policy Modifications**  
If we decide to materially change our Privacy Policy for ROZEE.PK, we will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site 30 days prior to the change taking place so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.

If at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please feel free to use our feedback form. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly answer your question or resolve your problem.  

**Contact Information**  
ROZEE.PK is the name under which Naseeb Networks, Inc., a Silicon Valley corporation with its principal place of business at 1299 Del Mar Avenue, Suite 260 , San Jose , CA 95128 and certain of its affiliated companies worldwide, do business. [Naseeb Networks, Inc](http://www.naseebnetworks.com/). is the legal entity which determines the purposes and means of processing the information gathered at www.rozee.pk. You can also contact us at support@rozee.pk.  
   
**Refund Policy**  
All sales are final. Refunds are solely at the discretion of ROZEE.PK . For further details email refunds@rozee.pk

Thank you for using ROZEE.PK.
